homeveda.com 2017-06-16

# Privacy policy - Homeveda

HomeVeda understands the importance of maintaining privacy of personal information of its users. This summary of our privacy policy is intended to give you an overview of: 

  * What information we collect about you
  * How we use your information
  * How and with who we may share information we have about you
  * How to contact us with questions or concerns 

**Information Collected About You**

We may collect “Personal Information” about you – such as your name, address, telephone number, email address or health information – in the following ways: 

  * When you register on the HomeVeda website or mobile apps 
  * When you sign-up for newsletters or other communications from us 
  * When you participate in an online survey 
  * When you provide personal information in comments or contact us section 

We may collect “Non-Personal Information” – information that cannot be used by us to identify you – via Cookies, Web Beacons, mobile applications and from external sources, even if you have not registered with or provided any Personal Information to HomeVeda. 

**How we use your information**

The broad idea is to understand you as user better and personalize your experience on HomeVeda properties. Specifically, we may use your information for the following: 

  * Administer your account
  * Provide your personalized content recommendations
  * Respond to your inquiries
  * Obtain your feedback
  * Statistically analyze user behavior and activity on HomeVeda
  * Send you newsletters, personalized emails or any other relevant information 

**How and with who we may share information we have about you**

We will not disclose any ‘Personal Information’ about you unless you specifically give us a permission to do so or in case needed for: 

  * To comply with any legal requirements 
  * Situations which can be considered as a threat to you or others 

**How to contact us with questions or concerns**

Please send us an email using the [Contact Us](http://www.homeveda.com//contact#) page.
